illogical: adj. 不合逻辑的，无章法的
Lesson 23. One man's meat is another man's poison. People become quite illogical when they try to
第23课。一个人的肉是另一个男人的毒药。人们试图
decide what can be eaten and what cannot be eaten. If you lived in the Mediterranean, for instance,
确定可以吃什么，什么不能吃。例如，如果您住在地中海
octopus: n.   章鱼, delicacy: n.   美味，佳肴
you would consider octopus a great delicacy. You would not be able to understand why some people
您会认为章鱼是一个很好的美味佳肴。您将无法理解为什么有些人
repulsive: adj. 令人反感的，令人生厌的, stomach: n.   胃, turn: v.   感到恶心，翻胃, fry: v.   油炸
find it repulsive. On the other hand, your stomach would turn at the idea of frying potatoes in
发现它令人反感。另一方面，您的胃会以将土豆炒的想法转向
fat: n.  （动物，植物）油
animal fat, the normally accepted. Practice in many northern countries. The sad truth is that
动物脂肪，通常被接受。在许多北部国家进行练习。可悲的事实是
most of us have been brought up to eat certain foods and we stick to them all. Our lives.
我们大多数人已经长大了，以食用某些食物，我们坚持所有食物。我们的生活。
abuse: n.   辱骂，责骂, snail: n.   蜗牛
No creature has received more praise and abuse than the common garden snail.
没有比普通花园蜗牛获得更多的赞美和虐待。
snail: n.   蜗牛, luxury: n.   奢移品，珍品
Cooked in wine, snails are a great luxury in various parts of the world. There are countless
蜗牛在葡萄酒中煮熟，在世界各地都是巨大的奢侈品。有无数
snail: n.   蜗牛, associate: v.   联想到
people who, ever since their early years, have learned to associate snails with food. My friend,
自从他们早年以来就学会了将蜗牛与食物联系在一起的人。我的朋友，
snail: n.   蜗牛
Robert, lives in a country where snails are despised. As his flat is in a large town,
罗伯特（Robert）居住在一个鄙视蜗牛的国家。当他的公寓在一个大镇上，
snail: n.   蜗牛
he has no garden of his own. For years he has been asking me to collect snails from my garden and
他没有自己的花园。多年来，他一直要求我从我的花园里收集蜗牛，
appeal: v.   引起兴致, shower: n.   阵雨
take them to him. The idea never appealed to me very much. But one day, after heavy shower,
带他们去他。这个想法从未对我很吸引我。但是有一天，大洗完澡后，
snail: n.   蜗牛, stroll: n.   溜达，散步
I happened to be walking in my garden when I noticed a huge number of snails taking a stroll on.
当我注意到大量的蜗牛漫步时，我碰巧在花园里散步。
impulse: n.   冲动, dozen: n.   12个，一打
Some of my prize plants, acting on a sudden impulse. I collected several dozen, put them in a paper bag
我的一些奖励植物突然冲动。我收集了几十个，把它们放在纸袋里
and took them to Robert. Robert was delighted to see me and equally pleased with my little gift.
并把他们带到罗伯特。罗伯特很高兴见到我，同样对我的小礼物感到高兴。
I left the bag in the hall and Robert and I went into the living room where we talked for a couple.
我把袋子留在大厅里，罗伯特和罗伯特走进了我们聊了一对夫妇的客厅。
snail: n.   蜗牛
Of hours, I had forgotten all about the snails when Robert suddenly said that I must stay to dinner.
几个小时，当罗伯特突然说我必须留下晚餐时，我就忘记了蜗牛。
fancy: v.   喜爱，喜欢
Snails would, of course, be the main dish. I did not fancy the idea and I reluctantly followed
当然，蜗牛是主菜。我不喜欢这个主意，我勉强遵循
snail: n.   蜗牛
Robert out of the room. To our dismay, we saw that there were snails everywhere. They had escaped
罗伯特离开房间。令我们沮丧的是，我们看到到处都有蜗牛。他们逃脱了
from the paper bag and had taken complete possession of the hall. I have never been able to look at a
从纸袋中完全拥有大厅。我从来没有看过
snail: n.   蜗牛
snail since then.
从那以后蜗牛。